나 내일 우리 아빠랑
저녁 먹으러 가는데 같이 갈래?
Hey, I'm having dinner with my dad
tomorrow night. Do you wanna come?
그러지 뭐, 너희 아빠 섹시하잖아
Sure, yeah. He's kind of sexy.
그런게 아냐, 나도 같이 있을 거야
Oh, no, I'll be there too.
그러면 신호 같은 거 정하자
일이 잘되면 너는 자리를 떠나
So we'll come up with some kind of signal.
If it's going well, you can take off.
넌 날 도와주러 가는 거야
임신했다고 아직 말씀 안드렸거든
No, I just need you there for support.
I haven't told him that I'm pregnant yet.
어머, 왜 아직 안 했어?
Oh. Why not?
분명 화내실 테니까
아빠 화내시는 건 정말 싫어
Because I know he's gonna flip out,
and I hate it when he's angry.
아빠 무서워하는 어린애 같아
Rachel, this is all so "Papa Don't Preach."
정말이야, 우리 아빠 무서워
한번은 담배 피다가 걸렸는데
No, Phoeb, wait. He's a scary guy.
I mean, one time he caught me smoking.
다시 한번 걸리면
한 갑을 다 먹게 한다고 하셨어
He said if he ever saw me doing that again,
he'd make me eat the entire pack.
헉! 그러면 같이 가줄게!
Wow. Well, I will be there.
아기를 먹게 하도록
내버려둘 수는 없지
Gosh, I'm not gonna let that man
make you eat your baby!
어, 저 남자 누구지?
어디서 본 것 같은데
Hey, who is that guy?
I think I know him.
아냐, 넌 모르는 사람이야!
No, you don't.
어머머! 모니카 독신 파티 때
왔던 스트리퍼잖아!
Oh, my God! Monica, he's the stripper
from your bachelorette party!
모니카의 뭐?
Her what?
비밀 독신 파티
Your secret bachelorette party.
- 독신 파티 했어?
- 저 남자 끈팬티를 이빨로 풀었지
-You had a bachelorette party?
-She untied his G-string with her teeth.
누구 나 좀 말려 줘!
Somebody stop me!
우리 독신 파티 안 하기로 했지
바보 같은 전통이라고 동의했잖아
We weren't having bachelor, bachelorette
parties. We agreed that it's a silly tradition.
그건 멋진 전통이야!
It's a grand tradition!
미안해, 쟤들이 나 놀래킨 거야
난 아무것도 할 수 없었어!
I'm sorry. They surprised me.
There was nothing I could do.
그러셔, 손으로 푸는 것 정도는
할 수 있었을텐데
Well, you could've untied it
with your hands.
불공평해! 나랑 가장 친한 친구
독신 파티 열어주고 싶었단 말야
This is so unfair. The one thing I wanted was
to throw my best friend a bachelor party..
근데 못했잖아
쓸데없이 스테이크 저녁만 먹구
but I wasn't allowed.
All we got was a stupid steak dinner.
웨이트리스를 집에 데리고 갔잖아
You went home with the waitress.
그랬지, 그날 밤 재미 좀 봤지
Yeah, that was a pretty good night.
어떻게 나한테 그 얘길
안할 수가 있어
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
결혼에서 가장 중요한 두 가지는
공개와 정직이란 말야
You know that the two pillars of marriage
are openness and honesty.
그 책 줘서 후회할 줄 알았어
I knew giving you that book was gonna
come back and bite me in the ass.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'스트리퍼의 정체'
- 우리 모로코식 치킨 요리시키자
- 아, 저는 고기 안 먹어요
-I'll order everyone the Moroccan chicken.
-Oh, I don't eat meat.
닭고기인데!
It's chicken!
- 닭고기도 안 먹어요
- 너희 레즈비언들은 참 이해 못하겠다
-I don't eat that either.
-I never understand you lesbians.
- 그래 새로운 일이라도 있니?
- 사실은요
-So, baby, tell me, what's new with you?
-Well, actually..
주문하신 74년산 라피트입니다
Your '74 Lafite, sir.
난 75년산 주문했어
74년산은 하수도물이야!
I ordered the '75. That's a
magnificent wine. The '74 is sewage!
나보고 하수도 물을
마시라는 거요?
Why would you bring me sewage?
어려운 질문인가? 자네 바보야?
그래서 웨이터나 하는거지?
Is that a hard question? Are you an idiot?
Is that why you're a waiter?
이래서 당신 시중은 안 들겠다고
매니저한테 말했다구요
This is why I told the manager
I wouldn't wait on you.
이봐! 애처럼 굴지마
Oh, come on.
Don't be such a baby.
눈치 못 챘을 거 같아서 그러는데
진짜 무서운 분이지
In case you didn't notice,
that is a scary man.
너희 아빠 말씀이 맞긴 해
74년산은 진짜 오줌 같거든
He's right, though.
The '74 is absolute piss.
이거 정말 큰 실수였어
말씀 못 드리겠어 피비 난 못해
This was such a huge mistake.
I can't tell him, Phoebe. I can't.
레이첼...
Rachel..
몇 년 기다렸다가
아기가 직접 얘기하면 되겠다
I'm gonna wait a couple of years,
and then the baby will tell him.
- 그럼 아기한테 막 화내실 텐데?
- 그거야... 아기가 걱정할 문제지 뭐
-Why? So he can get mad at the baby?
-Hey, that is the baby's problem.
- 웨이터는 괜찮아요?
- 모르지, 나야 화장실 갔다 온 건데
-Everything okay with the waiter?
-I have no idea. I went to the bathroom.
그래, 우리 딸내미
무슨 얘기인가 하려고 했었지
So, sweetie, you were starting
to tell me what is new with you.
저 티보 생겼어요
I got TiVo.
- 티보가 뭐냐?
- 임신이라는 은어예요
-What's TiVo?
-It's slang for "pregnant."
나한테 같이 오자고 할 땐
뭘 바랬던 거야?
Well, what were you thinking
asking me to come?
진짜 임신한 거냐?
Are you really pregnant?
예 그리고 아니오
Well, yes and no.
아니오는 빼고요
Except, not no.
그러면 '예'만 남네요
So to sum it up, yeah.
애 아빠는 누구냐?
이런! 설마 얘는 아니겠지
Who is the father?
Oh, no. Please don't tell me it's her.
아녜요, 로스예요, 로스
아빠, 로스 좋아하시잖아요
No, it's Ross. It's Ross. You like Ross.
잘 받아들여 주셨으면 좋겠어요
Daddy, I hope you're okay
with all of this.
생각해보면 좋은 일이잖아요
첫 손자를 보시는 거예요!
Think about it. This is a good thing.
This is your first grandchild!
할아버지가 되시는 거예요!
You're gonna be a poppy!
그렇지, 내가 할아버지가 되지!
That's true. I'm a poppy!
내가 할애비가 된단다!
I'm gonna be a poppy!
- 그래 결혼식은 언제냐?
- 누구 결혼식요?
-So when is the wedding?
-The who?
결혼식 말이야!
결혼식 할 거 아니냐
The wedding.
There's going to be a wedding.
내 첫 손자가 사생아가
될 거란 얘기는 하지 마라!
Young lady, don't you sit there and tell me
my first grandchild is gonna be a bastard!
- 결혼식 할 거지!
- 2월 2일이요!
-Tell me there's gonna be a wedding!
-February 2nd!
오늘 자기 강의하는 모습
정말 멋졌어
It was cool seeing you lecture today.
고마워, 근데 보니까
졸고 있었던 것 같던데
Thanks. Although it kind of seemed like
you were falling asleep.
아냐 눈을 감고 집중해서
완전히 이해하려고 했던 거야
No, I had my eyes closed so I could
concentrate and, you know, take it all in.
그래, 내 학생들이
그렇게들 많이 하더라
Yeah, a lot of my students do that.
- 이만 가봐야겠어
- 그래, 이따 저녁 때 보자
-I've got to get going.
-Okay, I'll see you tonight?
준보석 수집품 보여줘서 고마워
정말 근사하더라
Thanks for showing me your
semiprecious-stone collection. It's amazing.
맙소사, 네 잠 자리 실력이
굉장한 봐
My God, you must be good in bed.
너랑 모나랑 사귄 지 좀 됐지
잘 돼가냐?
So you and Mona, it's been a while now.
How's it going?
응, 잘 되고 있어
It's good. It's going good.
내 말은, 서로 잘 지내고 있어
모나는 진짜...
I mean, we get along great.
She's so..
- 죽여준다고?
- 귀엽다고 하려 했는데, 그래 죽이지!
-Hot?
-I was gonna say sweet, but yeah!
모나가 아기에 대한 건
잘 받아들였어?
She's okay with the baby?
실은 아직 말 안 했어
겁먹고 도망갈까봐 싫거든
I haven't actually told her yet.
I don't wanna scare her off.
솔직해질 필요가 있어, 안 그러면 너는
같은 길을 가고 있다고 생각하겠지만
You have to be honest. Otherwise, you may
think you're going down the same path..
사실은 서로 다른 길을 가게 되는 거야
but you're really going
down different ones.
그 책 뺏어서 패 죽일까 보다
I'm gonna take that book
and I'm gonna beat you to death with it.
있잖아, 자기 나를 많이
사랑하게 될 거야
Oh, my God, you are gonna
love me so much.
잘 됐군, 결혼해서 지금까지는
자기를 많이 좋아했을 뿐이니까
Oh, good. Because so far in this marriage,
I just like you a lot.
나 독신 파티 한 것 때문에
마음이 안 좋았거든
All right. I felt bad about
the bachelorette party thing..
그래서 자기한테 오늘밤
독신 파티 해줄 거야
so tonight you're gonna have
a bachelor party.
직장 동료가 이 전화번호를 줬거든
그래서 자길 위해 스트리퍼를 불렀어
I got this number from this guy at work and
I hired a stripper to come dance for you.
이 정도면 명예의 마누라 전당에
오를 만하지?
Am I going in the wife hall of fame or what?
- 자기 미쳤어! 스트리퍼 필요 없어
- 네 마누라 말 좀 하게 내버려둘래?
-Honey, that's crazy. I don't want a stripper.
-Will you let the lady talk?
그러지 마, 재밌을 거야
내 미안한 기분도 훨씬 나아질 거구
Come on, it'll be fun.
It'll make me feel so much better.
자기를 위해 파티 모자랑
포르노도 준비했다구
I got you party hats and porn.
우리 아버지가 마술사랑
눈이 맞았던 것만 빼고는
Throw in my father making out
with the magician..
내 14살 때 생일이랑 똑같은데
and it's just like my 14th birthday
all over again.
고맙긴 한데, 좀 그렇다
나 이제 독신 아니잖아
Look, I appreciate it, but it's a little creepy.
I'm not a bachelor anymore.
독신 파티라고 생각하지 말고
결혼 2개월 기념 선물이라고 생각해
Don't think of it as a bachelor party. Think
of it as a two-month anniversary present.
일주년은 지혼식, 2개월은 스트리퍼라
Sure. One year is paper,
but two months is lap dance.
내가 미안해서 그래
그냥 섹시한 여자 옷 벗는 거 구경만 해!
Please, I feel so bad.
Just watch the hot woman get naked!
- 알았어, 순전히 자길 위해서 하는 거야
- 앗싸!
-Fine, but I'm only doing this for you.
-Yeah!
그리고 조이를 위해서
And Joey.
- 고마워 또 누구 초대하고 싶어?
- 로스랑 조이만 해도 충분히 민망해
-Thank you. Who else do you wanna invite?
-Ross and Joey is embarrassing enough.
미안하지만, 난 못 가
오늘밤 모나 만나기로 했어
Actually, sorry, I can't even make it.
I'm seeing Mona tonight.
가짜 독신 파티 가려고
진짜 데이트 취소하는 사람은 없겠지
Who would cancel an actual date
just to go to a fake bachelor party?
미안해, 자기야
오늘밤 데이트 취소해야겠어
I'm sorry.
I gotta cancel tonight, baby.
미안한데 너의 상상 결혼식엔
못 갈 것 같아, 그날 바쁘거든
I'm sorry I won't make it to your
imaginary wedding, but I'm busy that day.
유니콘 세례식하고
요정의 성인식 선약이 있어
I already have a unicorn baptism
and a leprechaun bar mitzvah.
알아, 알아
겁나서 그랬어
I know, I know. I panicked.
내가 74년산 라투르인 것 마냥
우리 아빠가 나한테 소리지를까봐
I didn't want him to start yelling at me
like I was some '74 Latour.
라피트겠지
It's Lafite.
74년산 라투르는 맛이 좋거든
The '74 Latour is actually
drinking quite nicely.
저기 아빠 오신다, 말씀 드릴 거야
힘내야지
All right, here he comes. I'm gonna tell him.
I'm gonna be strong.
아빠 친구한테 방금 전화했다
I just called a friend of mine.
시일이 촉박하지만 플라자에
예약을 할 수 있을 것 같구나
I think I may be able
to book The Plaza on short notice.
정말요?
Really?
플라자에?
The Plaza?
우와, 아빠!
Oh, Daddy!
- 아, 맞다, 아빠 드릴 말씀이 있어요
- 뭔데 그러니?
-Right. Daddy, I need to talk to you.
-What is it, sweetie?
결혼식은 없어요, 로스랑 저
결혼 안할거예요
There's not gonna be a wedding.
Ross and I aren't getting married.
- 죄송해요, 아빠
- 그걸 말이라고 하냐!
-I'm sorry, Daddy.
-I don't believe this!
- 아빠, 제발 진정하세요
- 진정하게 생겼냐?
-Daddy, stay calm, please.
-How do you expect me to stay calm?
이건 용납할 수 없다, 레이첼
이유를 알아야겠다!
This is unacceptable, Rachel.
And I wanna know why!
그 자식이 너랑 결혼
안 하겠다고 하던?
Is it because that punk
won't marry you?
- 그런거냐?
- 네, 저보구 불량품이래요
-Is that it?
-Yes. He says I'm damaged goods.
결혼식 하는 거 긴장 되냐?
You nervous about getting married?
뭔 소리야?
What are you doing?
진짜 독신 파티인 척 하는 거야
결혼식 전인 것처럼, 재밌겠지
Let's pretend it's a real bachelor party,
before your wedding. It'll be more fun.
그러지 뭐, 내일 결혼을 한다니
믿기지 않아
All right. I can't believe
tomorrow's the big day.
다시는 다른 여자를 사귀지 못하는데
기분이 어떠냐?
How's it feel knowing you're never
gonna be with another woman?
매일 똑같은 얼굴 보면서
잠을 깰텐데 말야
Knowing you're gonna have to wake up
to the same face every day..
고마우신 죽음의 신이
해방시켜줄 때 까진
until you finally have
the sweet release of death.
네 말이 맞다
이렇게 하니 더 재밌다
You're right. This is more fun.
왔다! 자!
That's her! Okay, come on!
댁들 중 행운의 사나이
챈들러가 누구예요?
Which one of you lucky boys is Chandler?
저요!
That's me!
접니다
That's me.
저는 조이 트리비아니예요
열광적인 팬이죠
Joey Tribbiani. Big fan.
- 저기가 침실인가요?
- 예, 저쪽이에요
-Is that a bedroom?
-Yeah, right over there.
좋아요, 준비되는 대로 들어와요
All right. Whenever you're ready.
이상한데
That was weird.
- 저 여자, 왜 침실로 들어가냐?
- 아, 뭐해요
-Why would she go in the bedroom?
-I'm waiting.
- 그러니까, 저 여자...
- 그래, 홀딱 벗은 창녀다
-So she's a..
-Yeah, that's one naked hooker.
자기네 집 정말 근사해
이건 어디서 난거야?
I love your place.
Where is this guy from?
켈커타에서 가져온
18세기 인도 공예품이야
That's an 18th-century lndian artifact
from Calcutta.
우와
Oh. Wow.
자기는 공룡만 아는 게 아니네
So you're more than just dinosaurs.
훨씬 더 많이 알지
So much more.
어머! 미안해!
Oh, my God! I am so sorry!
괜찮아, 저거 그냥 가게에서 산 거야
Forget it. It's from Pier 1.
잠깐만
Sorry.
내 딸을 임신시켜 놓고
결혼은 안 하겠다구?
You think you can knock up my daughter
and then not marry her?
죽여버릴테다!
I'm gonna kill you!
지금은 얘기하기가 좀 그런데요
You know, this is actually not
a great time for me.
그래, 설명해 봐, 이 겔러 놈아
So come on.
Explain yourself, Geller.
- 우리 레이첼을 임신시켜 놓구선
- 레이첼 임신시켰어?
-First, you get my Rachel pregnant.
-You got Rachel pregnant?
- 누가?
- 네 놈이 그랬잖아!
-Who did?
-You did!
네, 제가 그랬어요, 근데 그냥 하룻밤
일이었어, 별거 아니었다구
Yes, I did, but it was a one-night thing.
It meant nothing.
아, 그래? 내 딸이 너한테
별거 아니더냐?
Oh? Really? That's what my daughter
means to you, nothing?
그게 아니라, 제게 소중해요
그러니까, 저 레이첼을 사랑해요!
No, sir. She means a lot to me.
I care.. I love Rachel.
- 뭐라구?
- 근데, 그런 뜻이 아니야
-What?
-But not that way.
사랑에 빠진 게 아니라
친구로서 사랑한다는 거야
I'm not in love with her.
I love her like a friend.
그게 친구한테 할 짓이냐?
문제를 일으키곤 결혼을 거부해?
That's how you treat a friend,
get her in trouble and refuse to marry her?
저는 결혼하자고 했었어요
근데, 하고 싶은 건 아니었어
Hey, I offered to marry her.
But I didn't want to.
하기 싫은 이유가 뭔데? 이런
거지같은 여자랑 같이 있으려구?
Well, why not? So you could
spend your time with this tramp?
거지같은 여자요?
Tramp?
미안해요, 그린 박사님, 여긴 모나구요
모나, 그린 박사님이셔
I'm sorry. Dr. Green, Mona.
Mona, Dr. Green.
저기 홀딱 벗은 창녀가 있다니
세상에나!
I can't believe there is
a naked hooker in there!
저 여자 창녀이기도 하고
스트리퍼이기도 한데
Maybe she's a hooker
and a stripper..
오늘 무슨 역할을 할 지
헷갈린 게 아닐까?
but she got confused
about what to do.
그럴지도, 스트립은 했잖아
우리가 못 본거지
Could be. I mean, technically, she did strip.
We just missed it.
저기요
Ma'am?
스트리퍼 일도 하시나요?
Are you also a stripper?
아뇨, 스트립 흉내는 할 수 있는데
따로 돈 내야 돼요
No, but I can pretend to strip.
But that's gonna cost extra.
따로 돈 내는 건요
수갑 때리기...
Okay, here's the extras:
handcuffs, spanking..
모니카가 너한테
장난치는 거 아닐까
Maybe Monica's playing a joke on you.
자기 남편한테 창녀를
불러 주다니, 재밌잖아
Getting her own husband a hooker.
That's pretty funny.
재밌기도 하겠다, 내 생일날엔
살인이라도 하겠구나
That is funny. Maybe for my birthday
she'll murder someone.
로스도 한 몫 거들었을 거야
일부러 바쁜 척 한게 아닐까
I'll bet Ross was in on it too.
I mean, he was "conveniently" busy.
- 여기서 담배 피워도 돼요?
- 아, 그게...
-Do you mind if I smoke in here?
-Actually, I'd rather..
에이, 피우세요, 그 방 어차피
불질러 버릴테니까
Yeah, go ahead. We're gonna have to
burn that room down anyway.
- 어떻게 나한테 숨길 수가 있어?
- 말하려고 했었어, 근데...
-How could you have kept all this from me?
-I was going to tell you, but..
좀 데리고 놀다가 레이첼한테 그랬듯이
이 여자도 차버리려고 했겠지
You figure you'd get what you wanted,
then you'd dump her like you did Rachel.
전 레이첼 버리지 않았어요
그렇다고 여전히 사귀는 것도 아니야
Hey, I did not dump Rachel.
Nor are we still together.
저것 좀...
Can I..?
그냥 자동 응답기가 받게 하죠, 뭐
Why don't we just let the machine get that.
로스, 나 조이인데
여기 창녀가 와 있거든
Hey, Ross, it's Joey.
There's a hooker over here..
우리 생각엔 네 녀석이
뭔가 알고 있는 것 같아
and we thought maybe you'd
know something about it.
아니야! 아니야! 아니야!
No! No! No!
아니야!
No!
좀 누워야겠어요
I need to lie down.
잠깐 할 얘기가 있는데요
Hey, guys, can I talk to you
for a minute?
사람들이 오리 스페셜
주문하도록 팍팍 좀 밀어봐요
Listen, again, I want to urge you
to push the duck special..
손님들이 오리를 안 먹으면 당신들이
먹어치워야 하니깐, 그건 싫죠?
because if they don't eat the duck,
you're going to, and it's not very good.
오늘밤이 그 거창한 독신 파티
있는 날이죠?
Tonight's the night
of the big bachelor party?
- 그 여자 전화 번호 알려줘서 고마워요
- 고맙긴요, 근데 누굴 위한 파티예요?
-Thanks for giving me that girl's number.
-No problem. Say, who's the party for?
- 제 남편요
- 남편한테 창녀를 불러 줬어요?
-For my husband.
-You hired your husband a hooker?
- 그 여자 스트리퍼잖아요
- 아녜요, 창녀예요
-She's a stripper.
-No, she's a hooker.
- 스트리퍼를 가끔 그렇게도 불러요?
- 스트리퍼가 창녀일 때만요
-Is that what they call strippers sometimes?
-When they're hookers.
세상에!
스튜, 어떻게 이럴 수가 있어요
Oh, my God.
Stu, I can't believe you did this.
창녀인 거 확실해요?
Now, you're sure she's a hooker?
아니라면, 제 경험상
가장 비싼 최고의 데이트였어요
It's either that, or she's just the best,
most expensive date I ever had.
모니카가 너한테 일부러
창녀를 불러준게 아닐까
Maybe she meant to get you a hooker.
왜 그런 짓을 하겠어?
Why would she do that?
네가 뭔가 배우길 바랬나보지
Maybe she wants you
to learn something.
네가 침대에서 뭔가 좀 서투르다
싶은 거 있냐?
Is there anything you're really bad at,
you know, sexually?
이건 진짜 최악의 독신 파티다
This is the worst
bachelor party ever.
- 뭐가 이리 오래 걸려요?
- 일 분만요!
-What's taking you boys so long?
-In a minute!
"일 분만"?
일 분 있다가 뭘 어쩔건데?
"In a minute"?
What's gonna happen in a minute?
그래 그럼, 저 여자한테
그냥 가라고 그래
All right. Maybe you should ask her
to leave.
- 왜 내가 해?
- 야, 이거 네 독신 파티잖아
-Why me?
-Hey, it's your bachelor party.
- 그러니까 당연히 네가 해야지
- 싫어, 네가 해
-Which is why you should do it.
-I don't want to. You do it.
좋아, 가위 바위 보로 결정하자
누가 저 창녀보고 가라고 말할지
All right. Rock, paper, scissors
for who has to tell the whore to leave.
- 왜 그래?
- 이런 거, 참 오랜만이다
-What?
-I miss this.
이런 건 한번도 안 해본 것 같은데
I don't think we've
actually done this before.
그게 아니고 너랑 이렇게 같이
시간 보내는 게 오랜만이라구
No, I miss hanging out with you.
- 우린 여전히 같이 지내잖아
- 예전처럼은 아니지
-We still hang out.
-Not like we used to.
기억나? 너랑 나랑은 뗄 수 없는
그런 사이였잖아
Remember? You and me,
we used to be inseparable.
근데, 지금은 달라졌어
You know, now it's like
things are different.
그래, 달라졌지
난 이제 결혼했잖아
Well, you know, things are different.
I'm married now.
오해는 마
너희들 결혼한 거 난 정말 기뻐
And, hey, don't get me wrong,
I am so happy for you guys.
그저, 우리 둘만 같이 지내던
때가 그립다는 거야, 알지?
I just miss hanging out.
Just us, you know?
그래, 나도 그립다
Yeah, I miss that too.
이제부터 우리 서로 같이 지내는
기회를 만들도록 하자구
I'll tell you what. From now on,
we'll make time to hang out.
그래 그거야, 이리 와
You got it. Come here.
세상에
Oh, God.
강도질이나 해갈까 보다
Listen, I am this close
to robbing you guys.
그 여자 창녀래! 창녀! 그 여자
She's a hooker! She's a hooker!
She's a..
안녕하세요!
우리 전화통화 했지요
Hi. We spoke on the phone.
너희 아버지가 찾아 오셨더라
So your dad dropped by.
참, 상냥하시더구만
He's a pleasant man.
- 이런
- 난 가는 게 낫겠다
-Oh, no.
-I better go.
바로 여기로, 싸움 구경을
놓치고 싶진 않거든
Just over here.
I don't wanna miss the fight.
로스, 정말 미안해
Ross, I am so sorry.
약속할게, 내일 아빠를 직접
만나서 수습하도록 할게
I promise, I will straighten this out
with him tomorrow, in person.
아니면, 이메일로 하든가
Or via e-mail.
문제는 네 아빠 아니라 모나야
그 자리에 있다가 질색팔색을 했단 말야!
I don't care about your dad. I care about
Mona. She was there and she's freaked out!
알았어, 그것도 수습할게
모나 이메일 주소가 어떻게 되니?
Okay, I'll fix that too.
What's her e-mail address?
알았어, 약속한다구 수습할게
맹세해, 내가 모나한테 얘기할게
All right, I promise, I'll fix this.
I swear. I'll talk to her.
좋아, 고마워
Okay. Thank you.
끝이야?
그걸 싸움이라고 하는 거야?
That's it?
You call that a fight?
"우린 헤어졌었잖아!" "아니었어!"
그런 건 다 어디 갔어?
"We were on a break!" "No, we weren't!"
What happened to you two?
다시 와 줘서, 정말 고마워
Thank you so much
for coming back over.
흠, 당신도 있군요
Oh, good. You're here.
불편한 자리가 될까봐
걱정했지 뭐예요
And I was worried that
it was going to be uncomfortable.
아녜요, 모나
제 말 좀 들어봐요
No, Mona, just hear me out.
우선, 우리 아빠가 당신한테
소리 지른 거 사과 드릴게요
First of all, I am so sorry
about my father yelling at you.
그래도 꺾이지 않았다고 들었는데
어떻게 그랬는지 얘기 좀 해줘봐요
But I heard that you held your own.
You have to tell me how you did that.
- 집중해
- 알았어
-Focus.
-Okay.
그래요, 로스랑 저랑 사귀었었어요
Yes, Ross and I used to date.
그리고, 맞아요
우리 아기도 가졌어요
And yes, we are gonna have a baby.
하지만, 우린 절대
다시 사귀지는 않을 거예요
But we are definitely not
getting back together.
- 내가 그걸 어떻게 확신하죠?
- 우린 서로 미치게 만들었어요!
-How can I be sure of that?
-Because we drove each other crazy.
로스는 소유욕이 강하고 질투심 많고
작은 일도 그냥 지나치는 법이 없어요
He was possessive, he was jealous.
He could never just let the little things go.
나, 이 여자랑 사귀려고
노력 중이다
Trying to date this woman.
하지만 로스가 얼마나
친절하고 자상한지
None of that compared
to how kind and gentle..
그런 건 비교할 수도 없어요
and thoughtful he is.
난 건들지 말고
You probably shouldn't touch me.
저는 이렇게 복잡한 관계에
끼어들기 싫어요
I don't wanna get in the middle
of something so complicated.
알아요, 하지만 복잡하지 않은
남녀 관계가 어딨어요?
I get it, but, Mona, what relationship
is not complicated?
우리 모두 짐이 있어요
당신도 그러실 테고
We all have our baggage.
You must too.
안 그러면, 왜 당신이 지금까지
짝이 없겠어요?
Why else would you still be single?
나 이제 가야겠다
I'm so gonna leave right now.
자기를 위해 이 문 계속
열어 놓아야 할까?
Should I leave this open?
아직 모르겠어, 왜 나한테
이런 얘기 다 안 했어?
I'm not sure yet. Why didn't you
just tell me about all this?
그거야, 이 일은 내가 자기한테
느끼는 감정과 상관이 없으니까
Because what's going on has nothing to do
with how I feel about you.
- 그래도 나한테 얘기했어야 했어
- 알아, 그러려고 했지만
-You still should have told me.
-I know, and I was going to..
레이첼의 아버지한테 듣는 게
더 나을거라 생각했어
but I thought it was better
that you heard it from Rachel's father.
내가 잘못했어
I made a mistake..
내가 자기를 너무 좋아하기
때문이었어, 정말로
but it's only because
I really, really like you. Really.
좋아, 이제 문 닫아도 돼
Okay. I guess you can
close the door now.
핸드백을 놓고 갔어
오오, 화해했구나
Forgot my purse.
Oh, you guys made up.
로스 키스 잘하죠?
알았어, 갈게!
He's a good kisser, isn't he?
I'm going!
그 여자 창녀인지
정말 몰랐어, 맹세해
I swear I didn't know
she was a hooker.
그 여자 여기서 담배 피우게 했어?
Did you let her smoke in here?
그 여자 엉덩이 자국이 네 할머니 이불에
찍혀 있는데, 담배 얘기나 할래?
Her ass-print is still on your grandmother's
quilt. Really want to talk about smoking?
있잖아, 내가 자기한테 보상해줄게
You know what,
I'm gonna make this up to you.
내가 스트리퍼 불러준다고 약속했지
I promised you a stripper..
자, 스트리퍼 나가신다
and you're gonna get a stripper.
- 모니카, 잠깐
- 왜?
-Monica, wait.
-What?
자, 계속 해
Carry on.
이 테니스화가 꽉 끼는데
These tennis shoes are so tight.
- 벗어야 할 것 같아
- 대사는 좀 꺼줄래?
-I think I'll take them off.
-Could you not narrate?
알았어, 선원 양반
Gotcha, sailor.
그 놈을 사랑하지 않는다는
이유만으로는
Just because
you're not in love with the guy..
- 너 아빠한테 사실대로 말했구나
- 한 시간쯤 전에
-You told your dad the truth.
-About an hour ago.
- 영화 보러 갈래?
- 그래
-Wanna go see a movie?
-Yes.
안녕, 아빠
Bye, Dad.
용납 못한다! 대체 사랑이
무슨 상관이야?
It's unacceptable! What the hell does love
have to do with it?
사랑보다 더 중요한 것들이
있단 말이다
There are more important things
than love.
아기 생각을 해야지
You have to think about the baby.
네 결정에 대한 결과에 대해서
생각해보란 말야!
You have to think about
the consequences of your decisions!
이봐요! 나도 내 결정에 대한
결과에 대해 생각한다구요!
Hey, I do think about
the consequences of my decisions!
당신이 무슨 권리가 있어서...
Well, what gives you the right to..?
지옥에나 떨어지셔!
Go to hell!
내 전화에 별 멍청한 놈이 다 있네
Stupid guy on my phone.